<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.0.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-02-08T15:48:21-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Data Driven Motorsport</title><subtitle>Speed, quanitified.</subtitle><author><name>Data Driven Motorsports</name></author><entry><title type="html">GTA Bound!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/s2000/shr/gta-bound/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="GTA Bound!" /><published>2020-02-08T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-02-08T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/s2000/shr/gta-bound</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/s2000/shr/gta-bound/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020/ridge.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;theridge&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You heard it folks, Data Driven Motorsports is headed for national competition levels
at &lt;a href=&quot;https://globaltimeattack.com/events/gta-the-ridge-motorsports-park-2020/&quot;&gt;Global Time Attack, the Ridge&lt;/a&gt; on June 13 and 14. For both of us, this will be 
our first national-level competition event. We’ve both dabbled around a lot with 
smaller organizations such as TakeoverNW, where we took home trophies in 2018 and 2019 (check out the times below). The Ridge is an especially wild track, since turn 1 can be hit at
over 100mph entry speeds. No replacement for just straight balls there. The first
half of the track is an assortment of double and triple apex corners with lots of elevation to 
keep it interesting. While the main straight demands power, it’s clear execution
and keeping up corner speeds will be critical for a winning lap. Check out a Porsche
GT4 lap for reference, it’s not far off our targets!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Courtesy of embedresponsively.com //--&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;responsive-video-container&quot;&gt;

  &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube-nocookie.com/embed/3tCMlZKPCHc&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real kicker here is, neither Andy nor Karl have been to the Ridge
before. Andy’s S14 has endured 18 months of solid dev time, in what’s ulimately resulted
in a 400+whp LS monster. With new suspension and fresh a 295 square set of [Yokohama A052s], he has his eye set on the Limited class win. Meanwhile, Karl has a more conservative goal of hitting a sub-1:55 lap in his NA S2000. It will be a classic battle of big tire, brute V8 power vs an 
agile, refined JDM icon!  We’ll keep you posted how it goes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/2020/throwback.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;timeslip&quot; /&gt;
Throwback to our first time attack event. Back in 2017, Andy still had a VQ in his S14, 
and Karl drove an MK7 GTI. Andy clocked 2nd in RWD, only behind an Alfa 4C and an Evo on slicks overall. The GTI didn’t have a bad showing either, beating out an 250whp, 1900lb EG hatch by
just 1/10th of a second!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Karl Taht</name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The S2000 Modlist</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/s2000/s2000-mod/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The S2000 Modlist" /><published>2020-02-08T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-02-08T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/s2000/s2000-mod</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/s2000/s2000-mod/">&lt;p&gt;Coming soon in full color.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Karl Taht</name></author><summary type="html">Coming soon in full color.</summary></entry></feed>